Hi, I'm Sean Carrell.
大家好 我是 Sean Carrell
In this lesson, I'm going to introduce you to Amazon's SageMaker service.
在这节课 我将介绍 Amazon 的 SageMaker 服务
By the end of this lesson,
学完这节课后
you should have an understanding of how SageMaker works,
你将明白 SageMaker 的运行原理
and you'll have had a chance to try it out yourself.
并且有机会自己操作 SageMaker
To start, let's answer three big questions.
首先我们来回答三个大问题
What is it? Why use it?
什么是 SageMaker？为何要使用它
How does it work? First, what is SageMaker?
它的运行原理是什么首先 什么是 SageMaker？
Well, practically speaking, a SageMaker is a combination of two very useful tools.
实际上 SageMaker 由两个非常实用的工具组成
The first is a managed jupyter notebook instance.
第一个是受管理的 jupyter notebook 实例
This is the same jupyter notebook that you know and love,
它与你知道和喜欢的 jupyter notebook 是一样的
except instead of running in a workspace or on your personal computer,
但是它并没有运行在 workspace 或你自己的电脑上
it runs on a virtual machine hosted by Amazon.
而是运行在由亚马逊托管的虚拟机上
As you've seen throughout this standard degree,
你在这门纳米学位课程中已经发现
notebooks give us a place to explore and process data and can be
Notebook 使我们能够探索和处理数据
used to test ideas before needing more sophisticated and powerful machinery.
并且可以用来测试一些想法 而无需使用复杂强大的机器
The second tool provided by SageMaker is an API,
SageMaker 提供的第二个工具是 API
which simplifies, some of them are
API 可以简化
computationally difficult tasks we might need to perform.
某些复杂的计算任务
Like, when want to train or deploy machine learning model.
例如训练或部署机器学习模型
So why use SageMaker?
为何要使用 SageMaker？
The simple answer is,
简单的答案是
that it makes a lot of the machine learning tasks we need to perform much easier.
它使我们要执行的很多机器学习任务轻松多了
For example, in the machine learning workflow you looked at earlier,
例如 在之前看过的机器学习工作流程中
SageMaker provides tools to make each of the steps involved simpler.
SageMaker 提供了让每一步都更简单的工具
The notebook can be used to explore and process the data,
Notebook 可以用来探索和处理数据
and the API could help simplify the modeling and deployment steps.
API 可以简化建模和部署步骤
So how does SageMaker actually work?
SageMaker 的运行原理是什么？
For the most part, when we talk about using sage maker,
在大部分情况下 当我们提到使用 SageMaker
we really mean working in the managed notebook.
实际上就是在托管 notebook 中操作
This notebook has all of the benefits that we talked about before,
此 notebook 具有我们之前讨论过的所有优势
with the added bonus of having access to the SageMaker API.
此外 还能够访问 SageMaker API
The SageMaker API itself can be thought of as a collection of
SageMaker API 本身可以看做一个工具集合
tools that deal with the training process and the inference process.
这些工具可以处理训练和推理流程
The training process is exactly what you think it is.
训练流程就是我们熟知的流程
A computational task is constructed.
系统会构建一个计算任务
Generally, this task is meant to fit a machine learning model to some data,
通常 此任务负责用机器学习模型拟合数据
then this task is executed on a virtual machine.
然后在虚拟机上执行此任务
The resulting model, such as the tree is constructed in
生成的模型（例如在随机数模型中会生成树
a random tree model or the layers in a neural network,
在神经网络模型中会生成层级）
is then saved to a file.
然后会保存到文件中
This saved data is called the model artifacts.
保存的数据称为模型工件
The inference process is very similar to the training process.
推理流程与训练流程很相似
First, a computational task is constructed for the purposes of performing inference,
首先构建一个计算任务来执行推理
then this task is executed on a virtual machine.
然后此任务在虚拟机上执行
In this case however,
但是 在推理流程中
the virtual machine waits for us to send it some data.
虚拟机会等待我们向其发送数据
When we do, it takes that data along with the modal artifacts,
收到数据后 虚拟机利用这些数据
which were created during the training process,
以及在训练流程中创建的模型工件进行推理
and performs inference, returning the result.
然后返回结果
So that gives you a basic understanding of the SageMaker service.
这就是 SageMaker 服务的基本运行原理
Before going into any more detail,
在介绍任何其他详情之前
let's actually use SageMaker to build our first model.
我们先用 SageMaker 构建我们的首个模型